{
  "category1": {
    "topic": "Math",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "How many blocks make up a tetromino?",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "The atmospheric CO2 in 1924 was 304.5ppm. How many times greater is it today?",
      "answer": "~1.38X, 421.8ppm"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Maximum squares can a queen can move to.",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "How many pentominoes exist?",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "405/2 = ?",
      "answer": "225"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": true,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "99/2 = ?",
      "answer": "92"
    }
  },
  "category2": {
    "topic": "Geography",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Isengard is nearest to which forest?",
      "answer": "Fangorn"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Mount Josiah is southwest of the larger Mount ____",
      "answer": "Chiliad"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Jah Keved is a region in which fictional world?",
      "answer": "Roshar/Stormlight Archives"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "If you find yourself beneath Skull Rock near Lover's Lake, where are you?",
      "answer": "Hawkins, Indiana"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Which country borders the greatest number of other soverign nations?",
      "answer": "China/Russia, 14"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "If you were from Erde-Tyrene, where did you lose The War?",
      "answer": "Charum Hakkor"
    }
  },
  "category3": {
    "topic": "Show Some Skin",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q1", true],
      "answer": "Bees - Beemo"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q2", true],
      "answer": "Cafe Cuties - Sivir + Soraka"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q3", true],
      "answer": "Winter Sports - Vancouver Amumu"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q4", true],
      "answer": "Storybook - Big Bad Warwick"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q5", true],
      "answer": "Arcade - Demacia Vice Garen"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": ["imgCat3Q6", true],
      "answer": "Anima Squad - Battle Bear Illaoi"
    }
  },
  "category4": {
    "topic": "First",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Byzantine Empire | Samurai",
      "answer": "Byzantine Empire [300-500AD] | Samurai [~900AD]"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Challenger Space Shuttle Disaster | Fall of the Berlin Wall",
      "answer": "Challenger Space Shuttle Disaster [1986] | Fall of the Berlin Wall [1989]"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "TCP/IP Internet | Compact Disc (CD)",
      "answer": "TCP/IP Internet [January 1, 1983]  | Compact Disc (CD) [1982]"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "3D Printer | Hubble Telescope Launch",
      "answer": "3D Printer [1984] | Hubble Telescope Launch [1990]"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Google | Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone",
      "answer": "Google [1998] | Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone [1997]"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Polio Vaccine | Disneyland",
      "answer": "Polio Vaccine [April 12, 1955] | Disneyland [July 17, 1955]"
    }
  },
  "category5": {
    "topic": "/10",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "IMDB Second Rated Movie",
      "answer": "1. The Shawshank Redemption 2. The Godfather, 3. The Dark Knight"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "IMDB Second Rated Show",
      "answer": "1. Breaking Bad, 2. Planet Earth II, 3. Planet Earth"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": true,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Any Top 3 Rated on Steam (Positive to Negative Ratio)",
      "answer": "1. Portal 2, 2. Stardew Valley, 3. People Playground"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Which Blade Runner Movie has a higher rating?",
      "answer": "Blade Runner 1982"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Any of Top 3 Rated Paid Game on Google Play Store",
      "answer": "1. Balatro, 2. Minecraft, 3. Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp C"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Any Goodreads Top 3 Rated Book (minimum 10,000 ratings)",
      "answer": "1. Words of Radiance, 2. HP Deathly Hallows, 3. Crooked Kingdom"
    }
  },
  "category6": {
    "topic": "Um, Actually",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Halo installations are overseen by Forerunner monitors, usually identified with a series of numbers followed by a name. 343 Guilty Spark is the monitor assigned to Installation 04, though before becoming a monitor 343 Guilty Spark was the Florian known as Riser from Erde-Tyrene. ",
      "answer": "343 Guilty Spark was built from Chakas, a human."
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Titus Groan is the heir of Lord Sepulchrave, the seventy-sixth Earl of Groan, in the castle Gormenghast. Titus has three sisters, Violet, and the twins Cora and Clarice. Finally, the mother Countess Gertrude can be seen roaming the grounds with her birds and cats.",
      "answer": "The first sister is named Fuchsia, not Violet."
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "August Kitko, titular character, is an excellent saxophonist who finds himself merged with one of the Vanguard Mechas from space. Using his musical ability he is able to communicate with the Mechas and act as a conduit in an effort to save the Earth.",
      "answer": "August Kitko plays piano"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Sonic and Tails are from Christmas Island, a real island in the Indian Ocean that served as the original inspiration for the series due to the unique geography and extensive nuclear testing during the WW2 era.",
      "answer": "Tails is from West Side Island, the westernmost point of Earth."
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Bill, Zoey, Franic, and Louis were in Fairfield, Pennsylvavia at the outbreak of the Green Flu, which caused significantly increased aggression and the loss of many higher brain functions. After discovering and defeating unusal new Infected strains, they make their way to the top of the Mercy Hospital and catch a ride on a helicopter. Unfortunately, the helicopter had little fuel remaining and it crashed just outside the city, leaving the group to make their way to Riverside on foot.",
      "answer": "Zoey shot the pilot because the pilot became infected. "
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Gordon Freeman earned a theoretical physics Ph.D. from MIT before eventually taking a job at the Black Mesa Research Facility with the hope of working on advancing teleportation. One of his experiments goes wrong, triggering a Resonance Cascade that ruptures space-time and allows Xen aliens to enter the facility. After defeating the aliens Gordon is taken by G-Man offered an ultimatum to die on Xen or work for him. Gordon accepts, and G-Man transports him shortly back to Combine-controlled Earth.",
      "answer": "Gordon was held in stasis for at least 20 years before the events of Half-Life 2."
    }
  }
}
